http://www.mstech-eyes.com/legal/privacy-policy

Legal | M&S Technologies
Toggle navigation
MENU
US Toll-Free: 877-225-6101 -- International: 00 1 847 763 0500
Effective April 1, 2007
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the M&S Technologies website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name Address Email address Phone number Specialty (etc.)
How We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order or information request. We do not share this information with outside parties.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and tune our service offerings.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How To Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing techsupport@mstech-eyes.com. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Since 1990, M&S® Technologies has served eye care professionals.
M&S holds US Patent Numbers 7,354,155; 7,926,948; 8,167,429; 8,419,184;
8,425,040; 8,550,631; 10,244,938; and 10,182,713. Other patents pending.
You may qualify for the ADA Tax Credit - Contact us to find out.
US: 877-225-6101 -- International:
00 1 847 763 0500
5715 W. Howard Street, Niles, IL, 60714 USA
©2020 M&S Technologies, Inc.
M&S | Melbourne Rapid Fields (MRF)
Clinical Trial Suite (CTS)
